near-death.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy of Near-Death.com

At   Near-Death Experiences and the Afterlife, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by   near-death.com and how it is used.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  [ webmaster@near-death.com](mailto:webmaster@near-death.com).

When accessing our website at   near-death.com,   Near-Death Experiences and the Afterlife will learn certain information about you during your visit. How we handle this information about you depends upon what you do when visiting our site.

If you visit our site to read or download information on our pages, we collect and store only the following information about you:

Log Files

Like many other websites,   near-death.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

 Near-Death.com currently does not use cookies.

Google’s DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve Adsense advertisements on   near-death.com.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve advertisements to users based on their visit to   near-death.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google advertisement and content network privacy policy at this URL:  [ www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Another advertising partner,   Amazon.com, may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

Third-party ad networks such as   Amazon.com use technology to generate advertisements and links which appear on   near-death.com and are sent directly to your web browser. These ad networks automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies, such as Javascript and web beacons, may also be used by these third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

 Near-Death.com has no access to or control over the cookies used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.   Near-Death.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

 Near-Death.com will never obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

If you identify yourself by sending us an e-mail containing personal information, then the information collected will be solely used to respond to your message.
